

Karen Simonyan

Full Stack Developer

I have been working with web development since 2014, the period during which I have worked in different environments, from big consultancy companies to start-ups. I am a self-motivated and self-taught professional who likes to solve problems. I merge a passion for usability and user experience with technical knowledge to create cool digital experiences. My repertoire includes programming languages and tools such as Angular, Vue.JS, Node.js, ReactJS, EmberJS, Mobx, Wordpress,PHP(Laravel, Codeigniter, Symfony, Zend, MySQL, MongoDB, PostgreSQL, Nginx and Apache server configuration, Gulp, SASS, LESS, Twitter Bootstrap, Susy, jQuery, and more.

developerkarensimonyan@gmail.com

Yerevan, Armenian

devkaren.github.io/

+374 77 965 765

20 June, 1996

in linkedin.com/in/developerkarensimonyan

SKILLS

HTML

CSS

Angular

/ue.js

Node.JS

Laravel

Codelgniter

MySQL

MongoDB

MariaDB

WordPress

Joomla

Rest API

WORK EXPERIENCE

Freelance Developer Workplace/Company

06/2020 - Present

Senior Full-Stack Developer ECRO

01/2020 - 06/2020

Senior Full-Stack Developer ERASOFTS

04/2017 - 01/2020

Full-Stack Developer SOFTCODE

09/2015 - 03/2017

EDUCATION

BA (bachelor's degree) IT security
NATIONAL POLYTECHNIC UNIVERSITY OF ARMENIA

2011 - 2015

Science and MathematicsHigh School

2009 - 2011